quietly close your eyes
the unspoken feelings stay alive
with light and smiles held still
feel this endless promise
I'll keep every light safe
I'll shine for only you, so bright
breathe in, and find your way to me
together forever, you and me
Step by step dream we chase
Side by side time and space
Hold me close never fade
forever with you, babe
Step by step dream we chase
Side by side time and space
Hold me close never fade
even if I waver, stay with me
weary nights, set me free
you already know without words
inside me, you shine
every night glows just like morning
falling asleep with you every night
Light it up future bright
Call my name through the night
with you till the end
I'll hold you forever
Light it up future bright
Call my name through the night
with you, light it up